[ominous, pensive music playing]
[ominous, pensive music continues]
[raider 1 speaks indistinctly]
[raider 2 speaks indistinctly]
[suspenseful music playing]
- You want to tell us why we--
- You're going out.
I need to send you guys out at dawn.
To do what?
- We're going to the other silo.
- [Juliette] Yeah.
I told Camille that I was gonna send
you there to bring the kids back, but I--
But you really want us to find out
where the poison is coming in.
- [Juliette] Right.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
Look, I can go by myself.
- No, I need two people on the job.
- [Kennedy] Wait, let me guess.
- You need two in case one of us dies.
- Yeah, in case one of you dies.
- [Kennedy] Great.
- Kennedy, I don't get you.
You spent three months screaming,
"Let us out."
And now you don't wanna go out?
No, no, no. I wanna go out. I just don't
give a shit about the rest of it.
[scoffs]
Here's an idea. I get Lukie here
safely to 17, can I do what I want?
And what is it that you want?
I want to go anywhere
but another fucking hole in the ground.
[Juliette] Okay, yeah.
You get Lukas to 17, you could do
whatever you want. I don't care.
That's great. Let's suit up.
[knocks on door]
[suspenseful music playing]
[door closes]
All right, uh, keep them out of sight.
I need you to get Danny Bly.
I need him to shut down the screens
in the cafeteria. Okay?
- Okay.
I'll be back.
- Hey.
What's up?
I went to Water Filtration.
There were guards outside,
which means
the drugs are already in the water.
How long until they take effect?
According to Bernard, immediately.
Start drinking milk, juice, wine,
anything except what comes out of the tap.
Whatever you're going to do, do it now.
I'm being followed.
Both on foot and by camera.
So,
we can't have any further contact.
Hey, Robert.
Be careful.
- [whistling]
- [door opens]
What are you two doing here?
We were with Danny
when the deputy messaged.
What's going on?
I'm going out.
Uh, we're going out.
- Oh, yeah. W-We're going out.
- What, why?
Well, uh, when Juliette went out,
she actually went to another silo.
[Kennedy] They know that.
The numbers in the helmets.
She went to Silo number 17.
Right, and 17 was basically dead,
except for some kids,
and she promised
that she'd bring them back.
Yeah.
You still wanna go out?
[Kennedy chuckles] Yeah.
Maybe you don't want to anymore, Kat, but...
but Danny and me,
we saw that cleaning video.
[scoffs]
Maybe that's something
in the glass of her helmet.
No.
You said that was possible.
I don't... I don't know
if it's good or bad out there.
I know someone who'd be
excited you get to go out.
[chuckles] Yeah.
[pensive music playing]
[Danny] You guys ever meet Kennedy's wife?
What do you think she'd say if it was her?
Oh, she'd only talk like that
if she had a couple of drinks in her.
[Danny] Doris wouldn't actually say
she wanted to go out.
- She was smarter than that.
- She's smarter than anybody.
She said if she ever killed someone...
[chuckles]
- ...probably him.
- [chuckling] Probably.
[chuckles] And if she ever got caught...
She'd have got away with it.
She said that if she got sent out
to clean, she'd go out singing,
happy to be free, be outside.
[inhales sharply] Even if it was just
for one fucking minute.
One fucking minute.
[sighs]
[door opens]
[Jerry] The suit-techs are ready.
Let's do it.
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music building]
I know I said you had until dawn,
I need you to go now. Come on, hurry up.
It's off.
All right. We'll keep the radio on
all of the time.
You'll hear me through your helmet here,
and I'll hear you on the radio,
but remember to talk in code.
Are you gonna be able to hear me?
I hope not.
- What?
- So, who am I?
You are dispatch. I'm Deputy Turley.
- She's Crane.
- Yep.
Uh, Im-I'm never gonna remember that.
- Can I be something other than Calso?
- Hey, Patrick. Hey.
Calm. We don't have time for that, okay?
Walk is only gonna talk to Lukas.
You're gonna get him to 17.
That's it. Okay?
He'll be fine. [inhales sharply]
[air lock door closes]
[air hissing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Lukas breathing heavily]
This is dispatch to Deputy Turley.
How do you read?
[Lukas] Uh, um... w-well...
Uh, the situation, uh...
Uh, it's a lot bigger than expected.
[chuckles]
There's nothing.
It's just nothing.
There's just nothing!
Hey!
What the fuck is all that?
[chuckles]
[Lukas, on radio] Deputy Turley here.
We're coming up on that next level.
[footsteps on radio]
[breathes heavily]
[Lukas] Dispatch.
We see the... the damage.
It's way worse than we imagined.
But we're-- we're gonna investigate.
Copy that.
[key buzzing]
[breathes heavily]
[breathing heavily]
[loud buzzing]
- [Kennedy] Do you hear that?
- What?
Do you hear that?
Hey, dispatch. [stammers]
We're hearing a-a-a buzzing sound.
Can you hear it?
[buzzing on radio]
[buzzing intensifies]
- [Lukas] Oh, fuck. Run! Run!
- [gunfire]
[Lukas grunts, screams]
[radio static]
Deputy Turley, this is dispatch.
If you read this, acknowledge.
Deputy Calso,
if you read this, acknowledge.
What happened? [sniffles]
It sounded like... guns.
- They have guns out there?
- [Juliette] No.
Radio them again.
There's no static on the line. It's just...
[breathes shakily]
[inhales sharply] Okay, um...
I don't know. Danny, can you just
get the screens back on, please?
I don't know. What if you
go down to the workshop,
and I'll come and meet you
if I-- if I can?
- Where will you go?
- I don't know,
but if I run, she's gonna arrest me.
So I-I have to stay.
S-So if, um... When she gets here,
Sandy, can you just say that I-I... I'm...
I've gone back home?
Jerry, is the combination the same?
[breathes shakily]
[beeps]
[The Algorithm] Lukas Kyle
and Patrick Kennedy have been neutralized.
What happened?
[The Algorithm]
You saw Nichols's unedited cleaning video.
What did you see?
Bodies.
What looked like an entire silo's worth.
And what does that suggest?
They were able to prevent a Safeguard.
At least momentarily.
"Momentarily" is the key word.
It is important to know,
for your silo's sake,
that the Safeguard is in fact
not preventable.
Let what you saw in the video
be evidence of that fact.
But that's...
that's what you think Nichols wants to do?
Block the Safeguard?
Talk to her.
Try to ascertain
if that fear is warranted.
If it is?
[knocking on door]
We agreed they'd be going out at dawn.
Yeah, um, Kennedy was agitated,
so I needed to get him out.
[Camille] Right.
Well, I'm sorry to have to tell you this,
but they didn't make it to Silo 17.
[inhales sharply]
Was there any other reason
you wanted people from our silo
to go to 17?
No.
Those kids saved my life, and I wanted
to bring them back here, so that's why.
- Nothing more important than that?
- Nope.
Mm-mmm. What could be more important
than saving children's lives, Camille?
Do you know what happened in Silo 17?
[ominous music playing]
[Juliette] No, do you?
[Camille] No idea. That's why I asked.
What the fuck happened out there, hmm?
To Lukas and Kennedy.
Suit malfunction, I believe.
- Suit malfunction?
- Yeah.
That's what happens when you rush.
Yeah.
We should've given them more time
to make the suits bulletproof.
[ominous music continues]
Charlotte?
What's happening? What are you doing here?
Hey, um... [scoffs]
- She can't tell you.
- I-I didn't actually ask you, yeah?
Sure.
Are you okay?
I'm all right, yeah.
Do you know who I am?
Of course I do, Daniel.
But I really can't say any more
until you do what Anna says.
[Anna] If you would both
- just follow me through these doors.
- Okay. After the ride we just had,
- we're not going anywhere with anyone.
- What is through those doors?
Lawyers. Many lawyers
with nondisclosure agreements.
Once you've signed, we'll get on the plane
and by this time tomorrow,
you'll know everything.
However, you won't be able
to tell anybody any of it...
- [phone keypad clacking]
- ...until we say so.
- [phone chimes]
- What, you...
You gonna sue me? [chuckles]
'Cause I have $700 in my bank account.
Gitmo. Half of the lawyers in there
are government lawyers,
which means that they can send you
to actual fucking Guantánamo.
And I'm not kidding. [sighs]
I've been there.
It's actually quite lovely.
I'm thinking about buying it.
The island. The whole island,
not just the... the base.
[exhales deeply] So...
I'm Per Stensen.
We know who you are.
Oh, I know. I'm just being polite.
My social team says I need to do that.
You're the journalist, right?
I've been told
that you have a lot of questions,
but I would love to ask you one.
Which would you prefer,
not signing the NDA and driving
out of here in a shitty rental minivan
not knowing anything,
or scribbling your name a few times
and getting to know
the world's most important secret?
[tense music playing]
I'll throw in $100,000
if that moves the needle at all.
$100,000. Of course.
The richest man on the planet,
and you're gonna give us
the world's largest secret for $100,000?
Okay, fine. A million, each.
- Oh, my... You can't just buy everybody.
- [Per] But only if you sign.
- You don't get anything if you don't.
- I don't know what is going on here.
All I want to know
is what the fuck happened to my sister.
Did you sign?
I did 'cause I also want to know
what the fuck happened to me.
Yeah.
So that's a yes from the congressman.
What say you, journalist?
How long before I can write
about whatever this is?
No more than five years. Hopefully less.
And I wasn't just being dramatic before.
This really is about saving the world.
Sure. [sighs]
Let's go save the world.
[people speaking indistinctly]
Ed Harwood.
[Ed] What's going on?
We need to speak with you, privately.
We think Orla Kent was killed
and then moved.
What we don't know
is how her body ended up here.
Well, it sounds like those cameras
you said were being shut down weren't.
Otherwise, how would you be so sure
she didn't just walk up the stairs?
Do you have any idea how--
How a body gets moved
without cameras picking it up?
I do not. [sniffs]
Unless...
Yeah, there was this guy in the Mids.
He used to put on a little show
for the kiddies.
He'd make something disappear,
and then poof, appear again.
Called it magic. [chuckles]
Maybe that's what happened. Magic.
We're wasting time. You want to go home--
Look, Sheriff. You just don't get it.
Here in the mines,
we got maybe six guys, two women,
who are just so fucking criminal,
this is the only place for them. Fine.
Mostly, it's just people
who did something stupid,
and they get sent here,
they get crushed by a rockfall.
Or they get fucking poisoned
by rat exterminators.
Now, the guy who did the magic,
making an egg disappear for some kids,
he was told by Judicial
that magic was a theoretical relic.
A theoretical fucking relic.
So they sent him here,
not for doing a thing,
but for having an idea.
What happens back in those tunnels, you...
It would be more humane
to hang people like him,
but no, they get sent here.
Each and every one of them
by your good old buddies in Judicial.
So...
obviously you don't respect me as sheriff.
[chuckling] Fuck no. [chuckles]
You respect Juliette?
At least she came from Mechanical
and had some dirt under her nails,
but as sheriff? Nah.
- Holston?
- [Ed] Holston? I respected him.
If he caught some idiot doing something
stupid, you know, he might let it slide.
He took into account people's families,
and what a stint in the mines
would do to them.
[Paul] Good.
I'm glad you respected him because
he thought you were a lousy crook.
He opened seven different
investigations into you.
Did he get me on any of them?
[tense music playing]
Hmm? Well, not such a lousy crook then.
[Paul] I saw you argue with Orla Kent
the day before her body was found
in your mines. Your daughter--
My daughter was lined up
to be the next head of Supply
until Orla Kent took her job.
So yeah, I was upset.
Glenda had a chance
to have a life away from all this.
But because a lot of people
in this fucking place
assume things based on
where someone's from,
or who they associate with,
that chance was taken away and given
to the lovely Miss Kent.
I said my piece to her, and that was it.
So, unless you got more evidence
than what's in that folder,
I would like to kindly ask you
to, uh, fuck off.
[breathes shakily]
Okay, you're here.
Come and have a look at this.
We have a lot of gunpowder left over
from the rebellion.
- We get a team into Judicial after hours...
- Right.
...wearing GWP uniforms,
and we scatter the explosives
along the wall to blow it open
along with all the pipes behind it,
including the one that carries the poison.
Okay, and then you release all the poison,
and then what? You have minutes to live?
- We can wear cleaning suits...
- No.
- ...under our GWP coveralls.
- Come on.
We'll look like maintenance men.
[Martha] We only have six suits left.
[Teddy] Look, it'll be tough,
but with a good team, I can get it done.
What about helmets?
I can cover them.
So how do we get six people
with helmets and bombs into Judicial?
'Cause I don't think the coveralls
is gonna be enough.
- Well, can Sims get us passes?
- [Juliette] But what about the gas?
That gas could be odorless.
It could be colorless, right?
The point is, Jules,
the new suits will give them an hour.
Yeah, a lot of people can die in an hour.
Did you think of that? Like, how many?
[Knox] It depends on how long it takes
to cap the pipe,
and how many people there are
on the levels above and below.
Those levels are residential.
People will be home sleeping.
[scoffs] Give us a range?
[sighs] Anywhere from a hundred to--
Could be a thousand.
Thousand people. No.
Better than 10,000.
Maybe we should just drink the water
and forget the whole fucking thing.
- Should we vote on this?
- [Bernard] No.
[straining] The people of the Silo voted
when they made Juliette mayor.
I need to think. I can't fucking...
Can you guys just figure out a plan
that doesn't kill thousands of people?
[door opens, closes]
You good?
There's something I gotta do.
We started with the most recent memories,
being in the Navy, the mission.
Iran. I thought he was gonna
leave that out.
He said there would be value
in remembering
right up to when I got into my plane...
but we keep the rest in a vault. So...
I know I flew the mission,
I know it went bad.
I know the facts, but it's kinda
like it happened to someone else.
Are you feeling okay?
I'm better than I was.
You know, Victor's helped me remember.
But he also made you forget.
I'm gonna try and get some sleep.
Sure.
Yeah, that was me asking you to move.
I need your seat.
[exhales deeply] Okay.
[gentle music playing]
How is she?
Well, she gave me some shit, so...
So better?
Maybe.
[Mark] I knew it was gonna be a bad day.
[Knox] How did my old man die?
And a good day to you too.
How did he die?
Didn't you go to the mines already?
Harwood said he got caught
in a tunnel collapse.
- Then that's what happened.
- No.
There was a bump in the way he said it.
There's something else.
Please.
Was he murdered?
No.
He's not dead.
Someone got buried in the mines,
but it wasn't your dad.
Way I heard it,
your father designed something
for Harwood.
In exchange, the next person to die
in the mines didn't officially die.
And your old man took his place.
What's the guy's name who died?
You start digging around
in Harwood's business,
you're likely to disappear
down a deep hole.
Do you know his name?
You wanted to see me?
Do you know where the Mission diary is?
I'm clearly no longer a threat.
Old habits and all that.
[Bernard] If you know where it is
and who has it,
bring them both here.
Please.
Can't sleep?
Uh...
Daniel and I slept in the back
of the minivan when you were driving it.
It wasn't me driving it,
and I know you didn't sleep.
It was bugged?
All right.
I didn't know what really went on
with your Post piece.
Good for you.
Yeah, well, don't tell anyone.
The NDAs cover everything
about everyone anywhere near this.
What's your story?
You wanna write a profile?
This is just my default mode.
Everybody's interesting to me.
I did my 20 in military intelligence.
Left. Started a firm,
which was very successful.
[inhales deeply]
Until it wasn't.
Entirely my fault.
Certain character defects
I hadn't addressed.
That's when I met the, uh... the senator.
It was her first congressional campaign.
I was her driver.
And now you're her loyal... what?
I don't really have a job title.
I just make sure that the senator
and her daughter are all right.
What does that mean?
It means a lot.
[pensive music playing]
What are you doing out here?
- You okay?
- I'm out here because we have a visitor.
She's had an experience
not dissimilar to your own.
What do you mean?
Camille drugged her as well?
[Bernard] Not Camille.
Robert and I...
we took her off the drugs
so that she could help the nurse
swap out your pills,
because she's the only one...
that can genuinely understand
what you've been through.
And I think she has a unique perspective
of the future facing us all.
Juliette Nichols.
Gloria Hildebrandt.
It's okay if you don't remember me.
They had me on those drugs so long,
I wasn't sure I'd-I'd ever remember
a single soul.
I asked Mrs. Hildebrandt here
because we need to talk about memory.
And because of what she holds
in her hands.
When I was head of IT,
Robert and I would track down relics
rumored to be sacred
for a secret group of citizens
known as the Flamekeepers.
George's mother was one of us.
[Bernard] People deemed a threat,
who sought knowledge of the before times.
And a revival of hope for a future
in a livable world outside.
We wanted just the truth, like you.
[Bernard] The two items we sought the most
were both documents of life
from a particular time.
A spiral-bound notepad
the previous heads of IT pursued
for 300 years.
It was never found.
The other was an obsession of mine.
The Mission diary.
What mission?
Mission was his name.
He was a porter, lived 140 years ago.
And during the great rebellion,
he transported the explosives
that were used to blow up the stairs.
Your friends weren't the first to do that.
[Bernard] Mrs. Hildebrandt,
would you read from near the end?
[paper rustles]
"I have a mark on my neck
and a scar on my stomach,
and I don't know where they came from.
I feel like I did know,
maybe even yesterday,
but now I can't quite remember yesterday.
I am afraid.
We've all forgotten so much.
Doctors keep saying it's a virus,
and it'll pass,
but it hasn't.
Things keep slipping away.
And anything I still remember
has gone hazy, like in a dream.
I don't know what I'd do without Allie.
We have each other.
But people who live alone,
I've heard they've stopped eating.
And so many have jumped from the stairs
that they've started hanging nets.
I swear if I ever f-forgot Allie,
I'd follow them over the side."
And that was his last entry.
[Juliette] I see what you're doing, and...
Yeah. It's fucking sad,
but I-- I told you,
I'm not killing a thousand people.
Salvador Quinn,
the head of IT at the time,
chose to drug the Silo
to prevent a Safeguard.
He never questioned the need
to erase people's memories,
but he also never denied the cost.
Quinn calculated that the terror and
disorientation from the forgetting drugs
resulted in the death of 2,000 people.
If you do not act, that is the cost.
I know you don't want to be the one
to make this choice.
- I know.
- Do you?
But the burden is on you to do it.
- You all right?
- [Charlotte] Yeah.
[Anna] You seem a little restless
back here.
Uh-huh.
Maybe you don't like flying.
I don't.
Unless it's me doing the flying.
- [chuckles] So a control freak?
- No, not at all.
I just like things done the right way.
[chuckles]
- What about you? You're not sleeping?
- Uh, it's just...
[inhales deeply] It's a big day tomorrow.
Yeah. What are we going to see?
You'd be awful at a magic show.
You'd be like, "Stop with the theatrics."
- Yeah, just get to the damn rabbit.
- [chuckles]
Can I get you anything?
- No.
- [chuckles] Okay.
But you could rub my feet.
[grunts]
[sighs]
- Sorry about, you know, earlier.
- No. Yeah.
I mean, I thought
you were Charlotte's doctor.
- Now I find out you're a part of this.
- No, no, no. I...
No, I am Charlotte's doctor.
And I'm still gonna need your help
in restoring
her childhood memories especially--
What if she only ever remembers
the last two weeks?
No, it will work.
Yet you said there was no guarantees.
I did, but two things can be true at once.
She's making great progress,
she really is.
[Daniel clicks tongue]
You know, when I was living
in Los Angeles,
all my daughter, Lulu, could talk about
was the Grand Canyon.
[stammers]
Begged us every day
for a month to go see it.
Finally, her mom and I caved in.
One Friday night after work
we took off on a road trip...
I was trying to get to the South Rim,
you know, before the sun rose.
I just kept thinking
how much Lulu would just love that.
Yeah. [chuckles]
I shouldn't have pushed so hard, you know.
I... I was tired.
So was Kevin Bishop.
And I didn't see his truck drift across
the center line until it was too late.
Daniel, all the techniques
that I'm using on Charlotte,
the drugs, the therapy,
I devised all of it 30 years ago
for myself because I wanted to forget.
- And I did, all of it--
- Yeah, but you didn't. You just told me.
Because we discovered in time
that you could choose...
you could choose what to keep,
what to leave behind.
According to the EMT report...
[mournful music playing]
...I held my daughter in my arms
as she died.
I didn't want to remember that.
And I haven't.
It works.
[Helen] Where are we?
[exhales deeply] Um, Atlanta.
Don't forget,
Anthony has to wear a jacket today.
[Anthony] Mom, no!
In your last class portrait,
you were all in jackets.
[Anthony] That was five years ago.
You looked very smart.
The artist did a wonderful job.
- [Sims] Camille.
- What?
Don't make him.
This is your decision now?
I was thinking it was his.
Fine.
Whatever.
[knocks on door]
Your mom must've forgot her keys.
[tense music playing]
What the fuck are you doing here?
- I told Nichols no more contact.
- Yeah, she said there's no camera here.
We need passes for Judicial.
For what?
Look, she didn't say, but she wouldn't
have me climb a hundred levels
if she didn't need them.
[Sims] Anthony, we got a change in plans.
You're gonna take the jacket.
- Dad, you just said--
- I just said take it.
If no one else wears one,
you don't have to.
Your mom is having a hard time at work,
and this'll make her happy.
Okay?
[worker] I have three of these in stock.
Excuse me. Sorry. I need a school jacket.
All right. Uh, what size?
Uh, I don't, uh...
Well, he's about this tall.
We're gonna be late.
Sorry about that.
I can carry the jacket if you want.
We'll get there on time, okay?
- Excuse me?
- Yes?
This is for Anthony Sims.
The judge just realized he gave him
the wrong one this morning.
[stammers] I'm sure
the one Anthony has will be fine.
Uh, that's his old one. It won't fit.
[exhales heavily]
Could I get the other one?
The judge would like to get it
to Recycling.
Just a sec.
- [Shirley] Did you get 'em?
- Here.
[Shirley] Great.
[Juliette] Thanks.
They gonna work?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
They're great.
- [panting]
- You okay?
You know the last time
I did that many stairs in one day?
Never, I've never done that.
[airplane landing]
- [Daniel] Here we go. Okay.
- [Helen] Okay, this is me.
Helicopters?
Yeah, the next part of our tour
requires we go slow and low.
And where are we going?
A property of mine not too far away.
It's 300,000 acres.
That's 400 square miles.
It used to consist of 42 individual farms.
You convinced 42 Georgia farmers
to give up their land?
I gave them generational wealth
that will take care of
their grandchildren's grandchildren.
[Daniel inhales deeply]
I gotta ask, that rumor going around?
[sighs] I am not a robot.
No, the other one.
- The unicorn.
- Oh, that one's true.
[Anna] Mom, we'll take the one
at the back, okay?
- I thought that was a joke.
- No, no, we have the science.
We created our own
gene-editing technology.
It makes CRISPR look like Fisher-Price.
We did some magic with horse,
narwhal and rhino DNA.
It would've worked too, but I scrapped it.
[scoffs]
So this mysterious whatever-it-is
on Georgia land,
how much of it's your idea,
and how much of it's his?
He's the brains. I'm just a believer,
doing whatever I can to help.
So, hopefully, once you learn
a little bit more, you'll become one too.
[helicopter whirring]
Let's go.
You had a momentary burst
of not wanting to be a mad scientist?
I talked with the tenth richest man
in the world.
And he offered me a billion dollars
if after I created my unicorn,
he could hunt and kill it.
Fucking billionaires.
They ruin everything!
[door opens]
Hey.
Oh, you took your jacket?
Dad made me.
How'd it go?
I was the only one
who even brought a jacket.
How do you think?
- Excuse...
- Hey--
- Hey.
- Anthony!
I'll talk to him.
[inhales sharply]
After dinner,
I need your help with something.
I have to go to Judicial Seclusion.
The nurse who jabbed Emerson is there,
and I need to talk to her.
I'd like you there as a witness.
- All right.
- Okay.
And thanks for getting him
to take the jacket.
- [Sims] Of course.
- Mm-hmm.
[Teddy, on radio]
Donny calling for the dispatch.
Go ahead, Donny.
We're heading out to make the delivery.
[Martha] Copy.
[suspenseful music playing]
[shushes]
[tense music playing]
[gasps]
- [radio beeps]
- Yeah.
It's Donny again. I got a bit
of an issue here with the delivery.
[Martha] What's the problem, Donny?
[Teddy] I just saw two big dogs
go into the apartment.
I mean, really big.
- What does that mean?
- [Sandy] Dogs.
Isn't that what people call
Judicial goons?
- [Juliette] What?
- [Sandy sighs] Does he mean Sims?
- His wife?
- What? No, no, no, no, no. No.
[Bernard exhales deeply]
We-We're not...
Are you sure you'll get another chance?
[mutters]
[sighing]
Just... [sighs]
Just go.
Copy that, Donny.
Proceed to delivery.
[suspenseful music playing]
What's this?
Boss has us servicing all the pumps,
level by level.
- It takes six of you?
- Any other levels? Nope.
But for Judicial we were told
to get it done in one night.
[tense music playing]
[Juliette] Hey.
[Bernard clears throat]
[Kennedy, on radio] Hey.
Yeah. Donny, what is it?
[Kennedy] Who the fuck is Donny?
Who is this?
[Kennedy] This is Deputy Calso.
- Um, here on, um... level 17.
- [whispers] Patrick.
Uh, Calso, this is, um, Deputy... uh, Crane.
Please continue.
Dep... Deputy Crane, yeah, okay.
So, uh, we had a little bit of a situation
here but, um, the kids are all right.
Donny? Donny, do you hear me?
This is dispatch.
Your delivery is no longer necessary.
Please return to base.
[Teddy] Shit!
- [Kennedy stammers] Who... Who's Donny?
- Oh. Calso, will you get off the line?
Please shut up. Donny, did you get that?
- [pants]
- Do you read me?
Your delivery is no longer necessary--
Stop! Stop!
[Martha] Please return to base.
- [crew member] Stop! Stop!
- [Teddy] Stop! Stop! Stop!
- Stop!
[pants] This is Donny.
- Yes. Go ahead, Donny.
- It's off. Returning to base.
[sighs]
[panting] Yes.
Martha, do you have anything to drink?
[Martha] I'll break out the good stuff.
[sighs, breathes shakily]
[mutters]
Calso. C-Calso, this is, um, Crane.
Can, uh... Can you hear me?
[chains clanking]
Could you please tell me what's going on?
[breathes heavily] Please.
What's gonna happen to me?
Amy, you need to shut the fuck up. Okay?
Camille, what are we doing here?
[Camille] What are we doing here?
I needed somewhere
where we couldn't be seen or heard
because we need to talk.
- Okay.
- [Camille] Okay.
I asked you to stop, Robert,
and you didn't.
I really don't know
what you're talking about.
You used our son!
The jacket Anthony came home with?
Not his.
Yeah.
[scoffs]
If you could stop putting
the forgetting drugs in the water--
What are you doing?
- That's all I'm asking you, is to stop.
- What are you doing, Rob?
- Tell me. Tell me what you're doing.
- You need to stop. Just stop.
- This drug could--
- Tell me what you're doing!
Can we discuss this somewhere other
than in front of her?
Oh, Amy? Fuck Amy.
- No, no! [cries] Please!
- [Sims] No, no. No!
- No. Please, don't-- Please!
- Tell me the truth. Tell me the truth.
- Please.
- [crying]
Like you haven't done as much.
I have done worse.
I have.
Whether you're right or... or I'm right...
Whether our son remembers me or not...
he deserves to have at least one parent
who hasn't killed someone.
[helicopter whirring]
[sighs]
What the hell is that?
[Thurman] Daniel knows.
[dramatic music playing]
Um...
It's a drill.
It's a very big drill.